Mom, how many degrees do you have and what are they in?
My initial degree is in science education with an emphasis in chemistry and biology.
And my second degree is my MBA from the University of Pittsburgh Cats Graduate School of Business.
Period.
Muggy, how many degrees do you have and what are they in?
I only have two.
Not only.
And they're in music.
The first one is a music education degree from West Virginia State University.
And the second one is from the University of North Texas in music education.
Thank you.
Aunt Chalzetta, how many degrees do you have and what are they in?
Oh, I have an undergrad degree from Tennessee State University in social science.
Okay.
An advanced degree from Texas Southern University in reading.
There you go.
I have two degrees.
My bachelor's is in sociology from Texas A&M University, GIGAM.
And my master's is in strategic communication and digital strategy from the University of Oklahoma.
Boomer Sooner.
Aunt Susu, how many degrees do you have and what are they in?
I have four degrees.
My undergraduate is public and international affairs.
My master's degrees are in economics and Latin American studies.
My PhD is in economics of education.
But I've never been...